<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Questionable Ethics Enhanced</name>
  <author>Mario55770</author>
  <packageId>Mario.QEE</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <description>
TEST

  If any of the past authors want me to take this down, I will do so. However, I made this so theres at least a 1.3 up today.
  Contains organ growing, organ extraction, animal/humanoid cloning, brain reprogramming... and all manner of ethically questionable stuff!
  Continuing KongMD's Questionable Ethics Enhanced, as it appears it was not updated to 1.3
  https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1787359789

 
  And now...introducing 1.5, the precepts update. Not fully implemented, but &lt;b&gt; you &lt;/b&gt;decide what is ethical now.(Or disable all ideology features in mod settings)
  Featuring nerve stapling enslavement, suppressing them fully, as well as knocking out most dangerous thoughts at the source(along with the pawn themselves...), precepts, and more.
  
  If you think that making human leather hats is too mundane, then this mod will spice things up.

* &lt;b&gt;Grow organs&lt;/b&gt; in vats!
* &lt;b&gt;Clone&lt;/b&gt; animals and humanoids! Clones have the traits and passions of their "parent".
* &lt;b&gt;Scan brains&lt;/b&gt; to preserve the skill levels of a pawn! Apply any brain template to your clones, to get them up-to-speed fast.
* &lt;b&gt;Recruit&lt;/b&gt; hostile pawns instantly with nerve stapling!
* &lt;b&gt;Balance&lt;/b&gt; the mod as you wish, with the Mod Settings menu

Thanks to Mehni for getting me answers to the questions I needed to get this thing done. 
Thanks StatistNo1(current mod dev at evolved organs redux) for dealing with my stupidity and assisting. 
Supports Alien Races out of the box. See the mod description page on Steam for more details!
</description>
</ModMetaData>